{
    "addition": [
        {
            "question":"5 + 11",
            "answer":"16"
        },
        {
            "question":"23 + 1",
            "answer":"24"
        },
        {
            "question":"9 + 23",
            "answer":"32"
        },
        {
            "question":"2 + 18",
            "answer":"20"
        },
        {
            "question":"3 + 21",
            "answer":"24"
        },
        {
            "question":"16 + 23",
            "answer":"39"
        },
        {
            "question":"5 + 20",
            "answer":"25"
        },
        {
            "question":"14 + 2",
            "answer":"16"
        },
        {
            "question":"24 + 24",
            "answer":"48"
        },
        {
            "question":"21 + 22",
            "answer":"43"
        },
        {
            "question":"7 + 23",
            "answer":"30"
        },
        {
            "question":"18 + 15",
            "answer":"33"
        },
        {
            "question":"7 + 4",
            "answer":"11"
        },
        {
            "question":"8 + 4",
            "answer":"12"
        },
        {
            "question":"7 + 8",
            "answer":"15"
        },
        {
            "question":"25 + 6",
            "answer":"31"
        },
        {
            "question":"13 + 25",
            "answer":"38"
        },
        {
            "question":"15 + 16",
            "answer":"31"
        },
        {
            "question":"20 + 13",
            "answer":"33"
        },
        {
            "question":"13 + 22",
            "answer":"35"
        },
        {
            "question":"3 + 6",
            "answer":"9"
        },
        {
            "question":"2 + 15",
            "answer":"17"
        },
        {
            "question":"6 + 16",
            "answer":"22"
        },
        {
            "question":"11 + 6",
            "answer":"17"
        },
        {
            "question":"22 + 19",
            "answer":"41"
        },
        {
            "question":"6 + 13",
            "answer":"19"
        },
        {
            "question":"21 + 19",
            "answer":"40"
        },
        {
            "question":"4 + 21",
            "answer":"25"
        },
        {
            "question":"2 + 23",
            "answer":"25"
        },
        {
            "question":"10 + 15",
            "answer":"25"
        },
        {
            "question":"10 + 5",
            "answer":"15"
        },
        {
            "question":"8 + 9",
            "answer":"17"
        },
        {
            "question":"14 + 7",
            "answer":"21"
        },
        {
            "question":"5 + 14",
            "answer":"19"
        },
        {
            "question":"6 + 22",
            "answer":"28"
        },
        {
            "question":"12 + 6",
            "answer":"18"
        },
        {
            "question":"18 + 10",
            "answer":"28"
        },
        {
            "question":"11 + 14",
            "answer":"25"
        },
        {
            "question":"2 + 6",
            "answer":"8"
        },
        {
            "question":"24 + 22",
            "answer":"46"
        },
        {
            "question":"12 + 16",
            "answer":"28"
        },
        {
            "question":"2 + 21",
            "answer":"23"
        },
        {
            "question":"24 + 19",
            "answer":"43"
        },
        {
            "question":"17 + 8",
            "answer":"25"
        },
        {
            "question":"4 + 3",
            "answer":"7"
        },
        {
            "question":"10 + 12",
            "answer":"22"
        },
        {
            "question":"1 + 9",
            "answer":"10"
        },
        {
            "question":"20 + 6",
            "answer":"26"
        },
        {
            "question":"7 + 6",
            "answer":"13"
        },
        {
            "question":"20 + 11",
            "answer":"31"
        },
        {
            "question":"19 + 12",
            "answer":"31"
        },
        {
            "question":"12 + 9",
            "answer":"21"
        },
        {
            "question":"23 + 10",
            "answer":"33"
        },
        {
            "question":"22 + 9",
            "answer":"31"
        },
        {
            "question":"17 + 10",
            "answer":"27"
        },
        {
            "question":"14 + 16",
            "answer":"30"
        },
        {
            "question":"8 + 10",
            "answer":"18"
        },
        {
            "question":"1 + 11",
            "answer":"12"
        },
        {
            "question":"24 + 2",
            "answer":"26"
        },
        {
            "question":"10 + 9",
            "answer":"19"
        },
        {
            "question":"11 + 2",
            "answer":"13"
        },
        {
            "question":"11 + 12",
            "answer":"23"
        },
        {
            "question":"1 + 4",
            "answer":"5"
        },
        {
            "question":"23 + 15",
            "answer":"38"
        },
        {
            "question":"1 + 25",
            "answer":"26"
        },
        {
            "question":"17 + 23",
            "answer":"40"
        },
        {
            "question":"3 + 14",
            "answer":"17"
        },
        {
            "question":"22 + 22",
            "answer":"44"
        },
        {
            "question":"21 + 21",
            "answer":"42"
        },
        {
            "question":"21 + 7",
            "answer":"28"
        },
        {
            "question":"1 + 14",
            "answer":"15"
        },
        {
            "question":"24 + 3",
            "answer":"27"
        },
        {
            "question":"15 + 8",
            "answer":"23"
        },
        {
            "question":"15 + 9",
            "answer":"24"
        },
        {
            "question":"24 + 10",
            "answer":"34"
        },
        {
            "question":"13 + 10",
            "answer":"23"
        },
        {
            "question":"3 + 1",
            "answer":"4"
        },
        {
            "question":"1 + 22",
            "answer":"23"
        },
        {
            "question":"5 + 5",
            "answer":"10"
        },
        {
            "question":"17 + 9",
            "answer":"26"
        },
        {
            "question":"25 + 20",
            "answer":"45"
        },
        {
            "question":"4 + 19",
            "answer":"23"
        },
        {
            "question":"10 + 2",
            "answer":"12"
        },
        {
            "question":"9 + 6",
            "answer":"15"
        },
        {
            "question":"25 + 8",
            "answer":"33"
        },
        {
            "question":"19 + 15",
            "answer":"34"
        },
        {
            "question":"24 + 8",
            "answer":"32"
        },
        {
            "question":"18 + 4",
            "answer":"22"
        },
        {
            "question":"22 + 11",
            "answer":"33"
        },
        {
            "question":"20 + 10",
            "answer":"30"
        },
        {
            "question":"1 + 24",
            "answer":"25"
        },
        {
            "question":"7 + 19",
            "answer":"26"
        },
        {
            "question":"21 + 9",
            "answer":"30"
        },
        {
            "question":"11 + 17",
            "answer":"28"
        },
        {
            "question":"18 + 7",
            "answer":"25"
        },
        {
            "question":"23 + 18",
            "answer":"41"
        },
        {
            "question":"19 + 13",
            "answer":"32"
        },
        {
            "question":"14 + 14",
            "answer":"28"
        },
        {
            "question":"2 + 16",
            "answer":"18"
        },
        {
            "question":"25 + 3",
            "answer":"28"
        }
    ]
}